Received request for unknown webhook: The requested webhook "POST soter-saas-chat" is not registered.
Received request for unknown webhook: The requested webhook "POST soter-saas-chat" is not registered.
Received request for unknown webhook: The requested webhook "POST soter-saas-chat" is not registered.
Received SIGTERM. Shutting down...
[runnner:js] Received SIGTERM signal, shutting down...
[runnner:js] Task runner stopped

Stopping n8n...
